Global Union Conference Video Recordings 6210 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Global Union Conference Video Recordings
2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bronfenbrenner, Kate
6210 AV
4.61 cubic feet
1.6 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
8255713
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 06, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Bronfenbrenner, Kate, 1954-
8255713
- Global Companies, Global Unions, 2006; 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Videotape 1 of 5. February 9, 2006.
- Global Companies, Global Unions., 2006; 2 (Box 1)
  Videotape 2 of 5. February 9, 2006.
- Global Companies, Global Unions., 2006; 3 (Box 1)
  Videotape 3 of 5. February 9, 2006.
- Global Companies, Global Unions., 2006; 4 (Box 1)
  Videotape 4 of 5. February 9, 2006.
- Global Companies, Global Unions., 2006; 5 (Box 1)
  Videotape 5 of 5. February 9, 2006.
- Tom Juravich, 2006; 6 (Box 1)
  Videotape 1 of 3. February 10, 2006.
- Meg Casey, 2006; 7 (Box 1)
  Videotape 2 of 3. February 10, 2006.
- Jim Robinson (Award), Pedro Wasiejko, 2006; 8 (Box 1)
  Videotape 3 of 3. February 10, 2006.
- Global Union Conference, 2006; 9 (Box 1)
  Videotape 1 of 3. February 11, 2006
- Global Union Conference, 2006; 10 (Box 1)
  Videotape 2 of 3. February 11, 2006.
- Global Union Conference, 2006; 11 (Box 1)
  Videotape 3 of 3. February 11, 2006
- 2:30 PM Crowne Plaza, NY, 2006; 1 (Box 2)
  2/11/2006
- 4:10PM Crowne Plaza, New York, 2006; 1 (Box 3)
  Audiocassette. February 11, 2006.
- 4:10PM Crowne Plaza, New York, 2006; 1 (Box 4)
- 2:30PM Crowne Plaza, New York: English Translation, 2006; 1 (Box 5)
- Speaker, 2006; 1 (Box 6)
  (1 of 2) February 9, 2006.
- Speaker, 2006; 1 (Box 7)
  (2 of 2) February 9, 2006.
- Crowne Plaza Manhattan, 2006; 1 (Box 8)
  February 10, 2006 2:30 PM
- Crowne Plaza Manhattan, 2006; 1 (Box 9)
  February 10, 2006. 4:10 PM
- Global Unions - English Translation, 2006; 1 (Box 10)
- Global Unions - English Translation, 2006; 1 (Box 11)
  (2 of 2) February 9, 2006